{
	"Subj_Name":"IMGT_Q1",
	"Quiz_Details":"",
	"Quiz_No":"1",
	"Quiz_Questions":[
		{
			"question":"Is an industry-standard programming language used to insert, retrieve, modify, and delete data in a relational database",
			"answer":["StructuredQueryLanguage","SQL"]
		},{
			"question":"contains statements for defining and administering the objects in a database",
			"answer":["StructuredQueryLanguage","SQL"]
		},{
			"question":"is the language supported by almost all database systems, and is the subject of published industry standards",
			"answer":["StructuredQueryLanguage","SQL"]
		},{
			"question":"developed by E. F. Codd while he was working at the IBM research labs in San Jose in 1971",
			"answer":["StructuredQueryLanguage","SQL"]
		},{
			"question":"This category of sql used to define and manage all the objects in an SQL Server such as databases, tables and view",
			"answer":["DataDefinitionLanguage","DDL"]
		},{
			"question":"True of False<br>CREATE,ALTER,DROP statements are example of DDL",
			"answer":["True","true","T"]
		},{
			"question":"This category of sql is used to SELECT, INSERT, UPDATE and DELETE data in the objects defined by D",
			"answer":["DataManipulationLanguage","DML"]
		},{
			"question":"This category of sql is used for Security commands such as GRANT, REVOKE, and DENY that control how a principal (user or role) can access a securable (object or data.)",
			"answer":["DataControlLanguage","DCL"]
		},{
			"question":"is the language containing the commands used to administer SQL Server, to create and manage all objects in SQL Server, and to insert, retrieve, modify, and delete all data in tables",
			"answer":["T-SQL","tsql"]
		},{
			"question":"True or False<br>Some databases are created automatically when you install SQL Server",
			"answer":["True","T"]
		},{
			"question":"True or False<br>The default system databases should not be deleted because",
			"answer":["theymaycausefailuretoyourinstanceofSQLServer"]
		},{
			"question":"This database keeps the instance of SQL Server functioning and holds the records all the system information for the SQL Server instance",
			"answer":["Master"]
		},{
			"question":"This database contains all information that is global to the server, including logins, error messages, system configuration, and the list of other databases that exist on the server",
			"answer":["Master"]
		},{
			"question":"This database store information about the scheduling of alerts, the definition of jobs, and the recording of the server operators to be contacted when a particular event occurs on the server",
			"answer":["Msdb"]
		},{
			"question":"This database contains all temporarily created stored procedures and tables and is generally used as a work area by SQL Server",
			"answer":["Tempdb"]
		},{
			"question":"This database is where tasks that require memory are performed, such as join and sort operations",
			"answer":["Tempdb"]
		},{
			"question":"This database stores a complete template for creating new databases",
			"answer":["Model"]
		},{
			"question":"When you create a new database, SQL Server copies the whole contents of the Model database into the new database you create",
			"answer":["Model"]
		}
	]
}